Noor Dai japanese Rooty Gann Busan Day sma glo rim te min tour
Noor Dai Japanese Rooty Gann Busan Day sma glo rim te min tour
Bouncer sender the breeze are free
保镖寄件人的微风是免费的
Days roo gnome pleaser sab world group is tree
Days Roo gnome Pleaser sab world group is tree
Mr. also sensitive work
先生也敏感工作
Soundproofing material with tier 9 your move to sd eri Cheese firth and me Female teacher
第9层级的隔音材料，您将迁移到sd eri奶酪和我那里女老师
Omasu
小增
Being able to do mediocre battles all day recognizes that kind of self, for example, sleep
一整天都能进行平庸的战斗就可以识别这种自我，例如睡眠
The time goes by, but the importance of time
时间在流逝，但时间的重要性
Do you feel
你感觉
Ore cheese one-man derepetition brown Come on weeks Ease
矿石奶酪单人重复棕色来几周轻松
Only a year
只有一年
2 years 5 years
2年5年
18 years 25 years
18年25年
Buiben n Buriburan Wizard wizard of y 2 jama Ironware booth Densuke
y 2 jama铁器房Densuke的Buiben n Buriburan向导
Rather than a ritual, it wouldn't be possible to grow plants without a religionist.
没有宗教信仰者就不可能种植植物而不是仪式。
[Music] Fave eaters Weedmans Everlasting Version
[音乐]喜欢的食客Weedmans永恒版
good prospect pou dou dou Dacedale cam n 1 to n total
良好前景pou dou dou Dacedale cam n 1至n合计
jr with Lee pumping boots prize tree
小李与李抽靴奖树
It ’s about rejuvenating the key, is n’t it?
是关于使钥匙恢复活力，不是吗？
You say that you let your hand out and make a gunshot.
您说您伸出手来开枪。
[Music] Tiaku Changer tiny please
[音乐] Tiaku Changer小请
pou dou dou
宝豆豆
first to
首先
Besponsor + Ponzu Bargram 5
成为赞助商+庞祖巴格拉姆舞5
During the war-I was a mountain bird around the 19th century, after all
战争期间-毕竟我是19世纪的山鸟
Because I was used to the kind of bonsai that my grandfather made from the Meiji era, which I used to do from water when I was little.
因为我已经习惯了我祖父从明治时代制造的盆景，当我很小的时候，我曾经从水里做盆景。
tree Zabu Old Amprose Sister March Booing Dowado Randy ny Clear pp 2 r 2
树Zabu老Amprose姐妹三月Booing Dowado兰迪ny清除pp 2 r 2
Even if the sentence dies, the bonsai I'm working on will survive, right?
即使这句话死了，我正在做的盆景也会活下来，对不对？
It's been a long time for horses, but it's good for children to go around.
骑马已经很久了，但对孩子们来说四处走走是件好事。
It was like this at that time, isn't it? The accumulation of time is amazing, after all.
毕竟，那时候是这样的，不是吗？
Memories are packed in that time
那段时间里充满了回忆
[musics]
[音乐]
ses Perth tr Audi used book xymax time off
ses perth tr奥迪使用过的书xymax休息时间